ambisafe.com 2019-04-10

# Privacy Policy

Privacy Policy
1. About this Policy
     1.1 We appreciate your interest in our products and services. Your privacy is important to us and
          we want you to feel comfortable with how we use and share your personal information.
     1.2 This policy sets out how Ambisafe Software Inc. (hereinafter referred as the "Ambisafe",
          “we”, “our” or “us”) handles your personal information, including when and why it is
          collected, used and disclosed and how it is kept secure (each and all referred to as
          "processing"). Ambisafe is a business to business product company that provides blockchain
          services, smart contract development, and tools needed for ICO platforms.
     1.3 You will find our contact details at the end of this policy which you can use if you have any
          questions, including how to update or access your personal information or to make a
          complaint.
     1.4 This Policy only applies to information we process. It does not apply to the practices of
          companies that we don't own or control, or employees that we don't manage. Information on
          our services may contain links to third party websites, and any information you provide to
          those sites will be covered by any privacy policies they may have. Please be sure to read the
          privacy policies of any third-party sites you visit. It is those sites' responsibility to protect any
          information you give them, so we can't be held liable for their wrongful use of your personally
          identifying information.
     1.5 This policy may change, so please check this page from time to time to ensure that you’re
          happy with any changes.
     1.6 This policy was last updated on 13 July 2018.
2. Your Personal Data and How We Use It
     2.1   If you choose to create an account (“Account”) with us, we require that you provide us
           certain Personal Information: your name (Last and First), country of residence, company
           name, company size, title, email address, phone number, mailing address, and company’s
           website. We will use your Personal Information to:
               •    Administer your Account;
               •    Process your payments and transactions;
               •    Provide you with the Site, the Services, and customer support;
               •    Tailor the features, performance and support of the Site and/or Services to you;
               •    Market products and services to you that we believe may be of interest to you;
               •    Respond to your requests, resolve disputes and/or troubleshoot problems;
               •    Improve the quality of the Site and the Services; and
               •    Communicate with you about the Site and the Services.
           We process your personal data because we have a legitimate interest in providing you with
           the best service, to verify your identity, and to comply with fraud and money laundering laws.
           Such processing is also a contractual requirement for you to use our services. Without such
           processing, you will not be able to use our services. Your personal data is protected by legal
           rights which are detailed in Section 8.

     2.2   We receive and store certain types of information automatically, such as whenever you
           interact with the Site or use the Services. This information does not necessarily reveal your
           identity directly but may include information about the specific device you are using, such as
           the hardware model, device ID, operating system version, web-browser software (such as
           Chrome, Safari, or Internet Explorer) and your Internet Protocol (IP) address/device
           identifier. We may also collect information about how your device has interacted with our
           website, including pages accessed and links clicked. We may use identifiers to recognize you
           when you arrive at the Site via an external link, such as a link appearing on a third party site.
           We process your personal information in order to satisfy our legitimate interest of enhancing
           security, monitoring and verifying identity or service access, combating spam or other
           malware or security risks and to comply with applicable security laws and regulations.
           Without processing your personal information, we may not be able to ensure the security of
           our Services. We collect some of this information using cookies – please see Cookies in
           Section 9 for further information.
3. Providing Your Personal Data to Others
     3.1   We may disclose your information to our third party service providers and other organizations
           for the purposes of providing services to us or directly to you on our behalf. We will never
           sell or rent your personal information. When we use third party service providers, we only
           disclose to them any personal information that is necessary for them to provide their service
           and we have a contract in place that requires them to keep your information secure and not to
           use it other than in accordance with our specific instructions. We will only share your
           information with the following providers under the following circumstances:
           •    We may share your information with Thomson Reuters, and Onfido, companies located
                in the United States, for identity verification services in order to prevent fraud. This
                allows us to confirm your identity by comparing the information you provide us to public
                records and other third party databases. These service providers may create derivative
                data based on your personal information that can be used solely in connection with
                provision of identity verification and fraud prevention services.
           •    We may share your information with Google, Mailchimp, Postmark, Intercom,
                DoubleClick, and Facebook, companies located in the United States, to help us with
                parts of our business operations such as marketing, and technology services. Our
                contracts require these service providers to only use your information in connection with
                the services they perform for us, and prohibit them from selling your information to
                anyone else.
           •    We may also disclose your personal data to our auditors, lawyers, accountants,
                consultants and other professional advisors insofar as it is reasonably necessary for the
                purposes of obtaining professional advice or managing legal disputes and risks.
     3.2   We may also transfer your personal information if we are under a duty to disclose or share it
           in order to comply with any legal obligation to detect or report a crime, to enforce or apply
           the terms of our contracts or to protect the rights, property or safety of our visitors and
           customers. However, we will always take steps with the aim of ensuring that your privacy
           rights continue to be protected.
4. Information We Receive from Others
     4.1   We obtain information about you from public databases and ID verification partners,
           Thomson Reuters, and Onfido, for purposes of verifying your identity. ID verification

           partners use a combination of government records and publicly available information about
           you to verify your identity. Such information includes your name, address, job role, public
           employment profile, credit history, status on any sanctions lists maintained by public
           authorities, and other relevant data. We obtain such information to comply with our legal
           obligations, such as anti-money laundering laws. The basis for processing such data is
           compliance with legal obligations. In some cases, we may process additional data about you
           to ensure our Services are not used fraudulently or for other illicit activities. In such
           instances, processing is necessary for us to continue to perform our contract with you and
           others.
5. How we Protect and Store Personal Information
     5.1   We store your information on our servers as well as on servers provided by Amazon Web
           Services ("AWS"). All services are maintained in the United States of America and all
           servers, which store your Identifiable Information, are secured and located in the United
           States of America. We use computer safeguards, such as firewalls and data encryption. We
           authorize access to your information only for those employees who require it to fulfill their
           job responsibilities and these employees are required to treat this information as confidential.
     5.2   We will take reasonable precautions, as well as physical, technical, and organizational
           measures in accordance with industry standards to protect your Identifiable Information from
           loss, misuse, unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration, or destruction. Information you
           provide is transmitted to and stored by us using industry standard methods for each type of
           information.
6. Transfers of Your Information outside the European Economic Area
     6.1   The information you provide to us is transmitted to, and stored at, servers in the United
           States. The information transfer is in compliance with the EU-U.S. Privacy Shield which is
           available at https://www.privacyshield.gov/welcome. The EU-U.S. Privacy Shield is an
           approved certification mechanism under Article 42 of the General Data Protection
           Regulation, which is permitted under Article 46(2)(f) of the General Data Protection
           Regulation. AWS is a participant in the EU/US Privacy Shield, under which transfers of
           personal data to the U.S. are authorized. You can access the European Commission decision
           on the adequacy of the EU-U.S. Privacy Shield at https://ec.europa.eu/info/law/law-topic/
           data-protection/data-transfers-outside-eu/eu-us-privacy-shield_en.
7. Retaining and Deleting Personal Data
     7.1   Personal data that we process for any purpose or purposes shall not be kept for longer than is
           necessary for that purpose or those purposes.
     7.2   Users may request the deletion of their account by contacting us at the address provided
           below.
     7.3.  In some cases, it is not possible for us to specify in advance the periods for which your
           personal data will be retained. In such cases, we will determine the period of retention based
           on the period we need to access the data for the provision of services, receiving payment,
           resolving your customer support issue or other issues or for any other auditing or legal
           reasons.
     7.4.  Notwithstanding the other provisions of this Section 7, we may retain your personal data
           where such retention is necessary for compliance with a legal obligation to which we are

          subject, or in order to protect your vital interests or the vital interests of another natural
          person.
8. Your Rights
     8.1  In this section we have summarized the principal rights that you have under the data
          protection law. Some of the rights are complex, might contain restrictions depending on the
          legal basis for processing the data and not all of the details have been included in our
          summaries. Accordingly, you should read the relevant laws and guidance from the regulatory
          authorities for a full explanation of these rights.
     8.2  Right to access: You have the right to confirmation as to whether or not we process your
          personal data and, where we do, access to the personal data. Providing the rights and
          freedoms of others are not affected, we will supply to you a copy of your personal data. The
          first copy will be provided free of charge, but additional copies may be subject to a
          reasonable fee. You can ask for your personal data by contacting our customer support.
     8.3  Right to rectification: You have the right to have any inaccurate personal data about you
          rectified and, taking into account the purposes of the processing, to have any incomplete
          personal data about you completed.
     8.4  Right to erasure: You have the right to the erasure of your personal data. We have described
          our policy for retaining and deleting personal data above in Section 7.
     8.5  Right to object to processing: You have the right to object to our processing of your personal
          data on grounds relating to your particular situation, but only to the extent that the legal basis
          for the processing is that the processing is necessary for: the performance of a task carried out
          in the public interest or in the exercise of any official authority vested in us; or the purposes
          of the legitimate interests pursued by us or by a third party. If you make such an objection, we
          will cease to process the personal information unless we can demonstrate compelling
          legitimate grounds for the processing which override your interests, rights and freedoms, or
          the processing is for the establishment, exercise or defense of legal claims.
    8.6   Right to data portability: To the extent that the legal basis for our processing of your personal
          data is consent, and such processing is carried out by automated means, you have the right to
          receive your personal data from us in a structured, commonly used and machine-readable
          format. However, this right does not apply where it would adversely affect the rights and
          freedoms of others.
    8.7   Right to complain to a supervisory authority: If you consider that our processing of your
          personal information infringes data protection laws, you have a legal right to lodge a
          complaint with a supervisory authority responsible for data protection. If you are a EU
          resident you may do so in the EU member state of your habitual residence, your place of
          work or the place of the alleged infringement.
    8.8   Right to withdraw consent: to the extent that the legal basis for our processing of your
          personal information is consent, you have the right to withdraw that consent at any time.
          Withdrawal will not affect the lawfulness of processing before the withdrawal.
    8.9   Without prejudice to the aforementioned, if we have reasonable doubts concerning the
          identity of a user exercising his/her rights referred to in Sections 8.2 to 8.8 or if we otherwise
          due to security reasons deem it necessary, we may request the provision of additional
          information and otherwise use all reasonable measures necessary to confirm the identity of
          the user.

    8.10  You may exercise any of your rights in relation to your personal data by contacting our
          customer support. Concerning "Right to erasure" users are also able to request the deletion of
          their account through our site.
9. Cookie Policy
    9.1   As is common practice with almost all professional websites, our website uses cookies, which
          are tiny files that are saved to your web browser, to improve your experience and to enable
          certain features, such as authentication. This section describes what information they gather,
          how we use it and why we sometimes need to store these cookies. We will also share how
          you can prevent these cookies from being stored, however this may downgrade or break
          certain elements of the sites functionality.
          Cookies may be either "persistent" cookies or "session" cookies: a persistent cookie will be
          stored by a web browser and will remain valid until its set expiry date, unless deleted by the
          user before the expiry date; a session cookie, on the other hand, will expire at the end of the
          user session, when the web browser is closed.
          Cookies do not typically contain any information that personally identifies a user, but
          personal information that we store about you may be linked to the information stored in and
          obtained from cookies. For more general information on cookies see the Wikipedia article on
          HTTP Cookies.
    9.2   If you create an account with us then we will use cookies for the management of the signup
          process, for general administration and for preventing abuse and misuse of our services.
          We use cookies when you are logged in so that we can remember this fact. This prevents you
          from having to log in every single time you visit a new page. These cookies are typically
          removed or cleared when you log out to ensure that you can only access restricted features
          and areas when logged in.
          When you submit data through a form such as those found on contact pages or comment
          forms, cookies may be set to remember your user details for future correspondence. In order
          to provide you with a great experience on this site, we provide the functionality to set your
          preferences for how this site runs when you use it. In order to remember your preferences, we
          need to set cookies so that this information can be called whenever you interact with a page
          that is affected by your preferences.
          We run an affiliate program and as a part of it affiliates advertise our site and services. With
          the affiliate program we use tracking cookies to track users who visit our site through one of
          our affiliate partner sites in order to credit them appropriately, and where applicable, allow
          our affiliate partners to provide you any bonus for making a purchase.
    9.3   You can prevent the setting of cookies by adjusting the settings on your browser (see your
          browser Help for how to do this). Disabling cookies will result in disabling all functionality
          and features of this site. Therefore, it is recommended that you do not disable cookies.
10. Automated Decision-Making and Information Collected Automatically
    10.1  Automated decision making means the ability to make decisions using technology, without
          human involvement. We may use automated decision making in processing your IP address
          and unique user, or session, ID for load balancing to determine which backend server will
          process the request. This information is required for us to perform your purchase contracts.

           Please note that the automated decision making we use will not have a legal or similarly
           significant effect on our users.
    10.2   We automatically receive and record information on our server logs from your browser,
           including how you came to and used the Services; your IP address; device type and unique
           device identification numbers, device event information (such as crashes, system activity and
           hardware settings, browser type, browser language, the date and time of your request and
           referral URL), broad geographic location (e.g. country or city-level location) and other
           technical data collected through cookies, pixel tags and other similar technologies that
           uniquely identify your browser. We may also collect information about how your device has
           interacted with our website, including pages accessed and links clicked. We may use
           identifiers to recognize you when you arrive at the Site via an external link, such as a link
           appearing on a third party site. We do not consider that this has any legal effect on you or
           similarly significantly affects you.
    10.3   You have the right to object to our use of automatically collected information described in
           this section. You can do that by opting-out of cookies and similar technologies in accordance
           with the method described above. If you do not want us to process your actual IP address
           (usually the IP address assigned to you by your Internet Service Provider) when you visit our
           website, you can use a Virtual Private Network (VPN) or a free service such as Tor.
11. Children’s Privacy
    11.1   Because we care about the safety and privacy of children online, we comply with the
           Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998 (COPPA). COPPA and its accompanying
           regulations protect the privacy of children using the internet. We do not knowingly contact or
           collect information from persons under the age of 16. The website is not intended to solicit
           information of any kind from persons under the age of 16.
    11.2   It is possible that we could receive information pertaining to persons under the age of 16 by
           the fraud or deception of a third party. If we are notified of this, as soon as we verify the
           information, we will, where required by law to do so, immediately obtain the appropriate
           parental consent to use that information or, if we are unable to obtain such parental consent,
           we will delete the information from our servers. If you would like to notify us of our receipt
           of information about persons under the age of 16, please do so by sending an email to
           privacy@ambisafe.com.
12. How to Contact Us
    12.1   The data controller responsible for your personal data is Ambisafe, a United States company.
           If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, your rights and/or our data collection
           practices, please contact our privacy office at:
    Data Protection contact details
    Ambisafe Privacy Compliance
    360 Pine Street, Suite 700
    San Francisco, California 94104
    privacy@ambisafe.com
